<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Meet Your Developer</title>
    <link>http://www.meetyourdeveloper.com</link>
    <description>Teaching personal branding and marketing to software developers all over the internet.</description>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Resume Should Be A Living Document</title>
        <author>Richard Rissanen</author>
        <link>http://www.meetyourdeveloper.com/posts/your-resume-should-be-a-living-document.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">/posts/your-resume-should-be-a-living-document.html</guid>
        <pubDate>10 Sep 2016 07:00 EST</pubDate>
        <description><p><em><small>By <a href="http://www.meetyourdeveloper.com/richardrissanen">Richard Rissanen</a> •
Follow: <a href="https://twitter.com/thekarmakazie">Twitter</a>,
<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/richard-rissanen-7684a867">LinkedIn</a></small></em></p>
<img src="http://www.meetyourdeveloper.com/assets/img/live-document.jpg" alt="picture of guy in a coffee shop with a computer"/><p>If someone asked for your resume right now, would you have it on you? If your resume is online, it is always available when opportunities present themselves. Imagine running into a potential client in a coffee shop over the weekend. They ask for something more formal than your elevator pitch. What will you give them?</p>
<p>If someone asked for your resume right now, would it be up to date? Opportunity is a fleeting mistress; you never know when she will show up. It is imperative that you keep your resume relevant. At <a href="http://www.meetyourdeveloper.com">MeetYourDeveloper.com</a> we suggest any event of merit should be a trigger to update your resume.</p>
<ul>
<li>When you finish a project? <em>Update your resume</em>.
</li>
<li>Learn a new language or framework? <em>Update your resume</em>.
</li>
<li>Released a new version of an open source project? <em>Update your resume</em>.
</li>
<li>Integrated with a popular third-party API? <strong>Update your resume!</strong>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Your resume should be a living document: always online, always up to date, and always ready when someone asks.</p>
<p>This is the first article in the series “Rethinking Your Resume”. Future articles will address such topics as: understanding and explaining your value, knowing your audience, leveraging alternative media, breaking from tradition, and other great ideas from the writers at <a href="http://www.meetyourdeveloper.com">MeetYourDeveloper.com</a>. Subscribe below to continue learning personal branding and marketing with other software developers all over the internet.</p>
</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
